[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the names of seven Goonies in the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "Data, Chunk, Stef, Mouth, Andy, Brand, Mikey", "incorrect_answers": ["Brad, Mikey, Mouth, Data, Andy, Stef, Chunk", "Mouth, Data, Sadi, Andy, Chunk, Brad, Mikey", "Mikey, Mouth, Data, Andy, Chunk, Sandy, Brad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The color named gamboge is a shade of this color.", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Grey", "Blue", "Purple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the Mexican-born director of the Golden Globe-winning movie Babel?", "correct_answer": "Alejandro Gonzalez Inarritu", "incorrect_answers": ["Guillermo Del Toro", "Maria Elaidia", "Alfonso Cuaron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The English language has quite a variety of words for the babies of different animals. What is the proper word for a baby swan?", "correct_answer": "Sygnet", "incorrect_answers": ["Weaner", "Keet", "Chick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Arrange the following oceans by their total area, starting with the largest:\n1)The Atlantic Ocean\n2)The Pacific Ocean\n3)The Indian Ocean\n4)The Arctic Ocean\n5)The Southern Ocean", "correct_answer": "2, 1, 3, 5, 4", "incorrect_answers": ["2, 1, 4, 5, 3", "1, 2, 4, 5, 3", "1, 2, 5, 4, 3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She was the fist celebrity to join the Barbie family.", "correct_answer": "Twiggy", "incorrect_answers": ["Cindy Crawford", "Jackie Kennedy", "Marilyn Monroe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1948 several cities in the USA had comic books burnt publicly.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Anakin Skywalker in Star Wars Episode 1: The Phantom Menace?", "correct_answer": "Jake Lloyd", "incorrect_answers": ["Ian McDiarmid", "Sylvester Styllone", "Hayden Christiansen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This moon of Saturn looks somewhat like a bulls eye if viewed from a certain angle because of the huge Herschel crater on its surface.", "correct_answer": "Mimas", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhea", "Tethys", "Ymir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Padme Amidala is the queen of which planet in the Star Wars universe?", "correct_answer": "Naboo", "incorrect_answers": ["Coruscant", "Alderaan", "Corellia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Francis Galton, half-cousin of Charles Darwin is credited with doing what, to tremendously help law enforcement agencies?", "correct_answer": "Being the first to use fingerprint  identification", "incorrect_answers": ["Using his knowledge of insects to tell times of death", "Aiding in the capture of top British criminals", "Developing the earliest form of DNA testing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the metric prefix kilo mean?", "correct_answer": "1000", "incorrect_answers": ["10000", "100", "1000000"]}]